Eze Onyemaechi Anthony

Backend (DJANGO) Developer Graphics Designer

Port Harcourt, Rivers State • 07067651557

Email: ezeonyemaechianthony@gmail.com

LinkedIn: linkedin.com/in/eze-onyemaechi-046162187

Pintrest: https://pin.it/5cizbKC

GitHub: https://www.github.com/iamExony

PROFILE

I am a growth enthusiast with strong desire to promote businesses and startups

through good designs. As a Graphics designer with a good knowledge of

marketing, I understand the impact that good design can have on sales, with

exceptional Imagination skill and creativity. With over three years' experience in

graphic designs such as church design, social media ads, branding and general

media design.

EDUCATION

B.Sc in Electronics and Communication Engineering

University of Port Harcourt, Rivers State

October 2019 till Date

Leekoms Global Resources

Graphic Design

September 2015

Deeper Life Skill Acquisition

Diploma in Website Design

July 2018

Sidehustle Internship

Backend Programming (Python-Django)

April 2022

Jobberman Soft-skill Training

2022

EXPERIENCE

Exony Brand, Graphic Designer

Sept 2019 - Current

- Responsible for the creation of logos, social media designs, church design, product design etc
- Ensure quality printing of design

Accomplishment

- We increased the sales of our clients through quality design.
- Understanding Users physiology, think like them, to solve their problems.

PATLINK COMPUTER, Manager

December 2015 – September 2019

Responsible for advertising the company to other startups

- Internet services and application
- Graphic Design and office suite
- Oversee daily operation of the company
- Training of students in Graphics Design

Accomplishment

- I improved the sales of the company through client's recommendation
- Proffer satisfactory solution to problems of clients

SKILLS

- Backend Development (python-Django)
- Adobe Creative Suite (Photoshop).
- HTML/CSS, Web Development and Joomla (3 years).
- Corel Draw
- Photography

PROJECT

- 1) Todo List App
- 2) MONITRACKA APP

Built API for Monitracka App (in-view)

LANGUAGE

English

• Igbo